{"tokens": ["Radisson", "Hotel", "Group", "has", "confirmed", "that", "it", "has", "suffered", "a", "data", "breach", "on", "affecting", "“", "a", "small", "percentage", "of", "our", "Radisson", "Rewards", "members", "”", ".", "Business", "Traveller", "was", "alerted", "to", "the", "incident", "by", "one", "of", "our", "readers", ",", "who", "had", "received", "an", "email", "from", "Radisson", "confirming", "that", "his", "details", "had", "been", "compromised", ".", "Radisson", "says", "that", "it", "identified", "the", "breach", "on", "October", "1", ",", "although", "it", "’s", "not", "clear", "exactly", "when", "the", "incident", "occured", ".", "A", "statement", "on", "the", "group", "’s", "website", "states", ":", "“", "This", "data", "security", "incident", "did", "not", "compromise", "any", "credit", "card", "or", "password", "information", ".", "Our", "ongoing", "investigation", "has", "determined", "that", "the", "information", "accessed", "was", "restricted", "to", "member", "name", ",", "address", "(", "including", "country", "of", "residence", ")", ",", "email", "address", ",", "and", "in", "some", "cases", ",", "company", "name", ",", "phone", "number", ",", "Radisson", "Rewards", "member", "number", "and", "any", "frequent", "flyer", "numbers", "on", "file", ".", "“", "Upon", "identifying", "this", "issue", "Radisson", "Rewards", "immediately", "revoked", "access", "to", "the", "unauthorized", "person", "(", "s", ")", ".", "All", "impacted", "member", "accounts", "have", "been", "secured", "and", "flagged", "to", "monitor", "for", "any", "potential", "unauthorized", "behavior", ".", "“", "While", "the", "ongoing", "risk", "to", "your", "Radisson", "Rewards", "account", "is", "low", ",", "please", "monitor", "your", "account", "for", "any", "suspicious", "activity", ".", "You", "should", "also", "be", "aware", "that", "third", "parties", "may", "claim", "to", "be", "Radisson", "Rewards", "and", "attempt", "to", "gather", "personal", "information", "by", "deception", "(", "known", "as", "“", "phishing", "”", ")", ",", "including", "through", "the", "use", "of", "links", "to", "fake", "websites", ".", "Radisson", "Rewards", "will", "not", "ask", "for", "your", "password", "or", "user", "information", "to", "be", "provided", "in", "an", "e-mail", ".", "“", "Radisson", "Rewards", "takes", "this", "incident", "very", "seriously", "and", "is", "conducting", "an", "ongoing", "extensive", "investigation", "into", "the", "incident", "to", "help", "prevent", "data", "privacy", "incidents", "from", "happening", "again", "in", "the", "future", ".", "”", "Radisson", "says", "that", "affected", "members", "will", "have", "receives", "an", "email", "notification", "from", "Radisson", "Rewards", "either", "yesterday", "(", "October", "30", ")", "or", "today", "(", "October", "31", ")", ".", "In", "the", "FAQs", "Radisson", "stresses", "that", "credit", "card", "data", "was", "not", "exposed", "by", "the", "breach", ",", "nor", "were", "members", "’", "passwords", "or", "travel", "histories", "/", "future", "stays", ".", "The", "hotel", "group", "is", "the", "latest", "in", "a", "line", "of", "travel", "companies", "to", "suffer", "data", "breaches", ",", "with", "British", "Airways", "and", "Cathay", "Pacific", "both", "admitting", "to", "compromised", "data", "in", "the", "last", "couple", "of", "months", "."], "trigger": [{"start": 9, "end": 11, "text": ["a", "data", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 49, "end": 51, "text": ["had", "been", "compromised"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 91, "end": 91, "text": ["compromise"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 106, "end": 107, "text": ["information", "accessed"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 333, "end": 336, "text": ["exposed", "by", "the", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 364, "end": 365, "text": ["data", "breaches"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 376, "end": 376, "text": ["compromised"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 214, "end": 216, "text": ["claim", "to", "be"], "event": "Phishing"}, {"start": 231, "end": 231, "text": ["phishing"], "event": "Phishing"}], "Entities": [[{"start": 0, "end": 2, "text": ["Radisson", "Hotel", "Group"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 6, "end": 6, "text": ["it"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 20, "end": 22, "text": ["Radisson", "Rewards", "members"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 47, "end": 48, "text": ["his", "details"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 33, "end": 36, "text": ["one", "of", "our", "readers"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 93, "end": 94, "text": ["credit", "card"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 96, "end": 97, "text": ["password", "information"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 142, "end": 144, "text": ["frequent", "flyer", "numbers"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 136, "end": 139, "text": ["Radisson", "Rewards", "member", "number"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 133, "end": 134, "text": ["phone", "number"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 130, "end": 131, "text": ["company", "name"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 111, "end": 112, "text": ["member", "name"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 114, "end": 114, "text": ["address"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 122, "end": 123, "text": ["email", "address"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 328, "end": 330, "text": ["credit", "card", "data"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 342, "end": 342, "text": ["passwords"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 344, "end": 345, "text": ["travel", "histories"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 347, "end": 348, "text": ["future", "stays"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 340, "end": 340, "text": ["members"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 351, "end": 352, "text": ["hotel", "group"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 360, "end": 361, "text": ["travel", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 368, "end": 369, "text": ["British", "Airways"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 371, "end": 372, "text": ["Cathay", "Pacific"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 377, "end": 377, "text": ["data"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 380, "end": 383, "text": ["last", "couple", "of", "months"], "type": "Time"}], [{"start": 211, "end": 212, "text": ["third", "parties"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 222, "end": 224, "text": ["gather", "personal", "information"], "type": "Purpose"}, {"start": 226, "end": 226, "text": ["deception"], "type": "Capabilities"}, {"start": 236, "end": 243, "text": ["through", "the", "use", "of", "links", "to", "fake", "websites"], "type": "Capabilities"}, {"start": 217, "end": 218, "text": ["Radisson", "Rewards"], "type": "Organization"}], []], "Causal": [[], [], [], [], [], [], [], [{"start": 211, "end": 212, "text": ["third", "parties"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 226, "end": 226, "text": ["deception"], "type": "Capabilities"}, {"start": 236, "end": 243, "text": ["through", "the", "use", "of", "links", "to", "fake", "websites"], "type": "Capabilities"}], []], "Effect": [[{"start": 0, "end": 2, "text": ["Radisson", "Hotel", "Group"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 20, "end": 22, "text": ["Radisson", "Rewards", "members"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 47, "end": 48, "text": ["his", "details"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 33, "end": 36, "text": ["one", "of", "our", "readers"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 93, "end": 94, "text": ["credit", "card"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 96, "end": 97, "text": ["password", "information"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 142, "end": 144, "text": ["frequent", "flyer", "numbers"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 136, "end": 139, "text": ["Radisson", "Rewards", "member", "number"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 133, "end": 134, "text": ["phone", "number"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 130, "end": 131, "text": ["company", "name"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 111, "end": 112, "text": ["member", "name"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 114, "end": 114, "text": ["address"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 122, "end": 123, "text": ["email", "address"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 328, "end": 330, "text": ["credit", "card", "data"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 342, "end": 342, "text": ["passwords"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 344, "end": 345, "text": ["travel", "histories"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 347, "end": 348, "text": ["future", "stays"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 340, "end": 340, "text": ["members"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 351, "end": 352, "text": ["hotel", "group"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 360, "end": 361, "text": ["travel", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 368, "end": 369, "text": ["British", "Airways"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 371, "end": 372, "text": ["Cathay", "Pacific"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 377, "end": 377, "text": ["data"], "type": "Data"}], [{"start": 222, "end": 224, "text": ["gather", "personal", "information"], "type": "Purpose"}], []]}