{"tokens": ["JobStreet", "is", "informing", "clients", "by", "email", "whether", "they", "were", "caught", "up", "in", "a", "Malaysia", "-", "based", "data", "breach", "that", "affected", "19", "different", "companies", ".", "“", "We", "are", "writing", "to", "notify", "you", "that", "we", "recently", "identified", "a", "post", "claiming", "that", "personal", "information", "from", "the", "databases", "of", "19", "corporations", "and", "associations", "had", "been", "made", "public", ",", "including", "ours", ",", "”", "the", "email", "says", ".", "According", "to", "website", "haveibeenpwned.com", ",", "3,883,455", "JobStreet", "accounts", "were", "affected", "by", "the", "breach", ".", "It", "says", "the", "information", "was", "freely", "downloadable", "on", "a", "Tor", "hidden", "service", ".", "The", "breach", "also", "affected", "more", "than", "46", "million", "Malaysian", "users", "and", "several", "telecommunications", "companies", ".", "Telecommunications", "providers", "caught", "by", "the", "breach", "include", "Altel", ",", "Celcom", ",", "DiGi", ",", "EnablingAsia", ",", "Friendi", ",", "Maxis", ",", "Merchantrade", "Asia", ",", "PLDT", ",", "Redtone", ",", "Tunetalk", ",", "Umobile", "and", "XoX", ",", "reports", "suggest", ".", "It", "also", "affected", "organisations", "such", "as", "the", "Academy", "of", "Medicine", "Malaysia", ",", "the", "Malaysian", "Dental", "Association", ",", "the", "Malaysian", "Medical", "Association", ",", "and", "the", "National", "Specialist", "Register", "of", "Malaysia", ".", "Reports", "speculate", "that", "more", "than", "81,000", "records", "were", "stolen", "from", "these", "organisations", ".", "“", "Our", "investigations", "established", "that", "some", "personal", "candidate", "information", "pertaining", "to", "accounts", "created", "before", "July", "2012", "has", "been", "exposed", ".", "To", "help", "protect", "our", "customers", ",", "the", "team", "is", "continuously", "enhancing", "our", "security", "measures", "for", "all", "user", "information", "stored", "with", "JobStreet.com", ",", "”", "JobStreet", "CEO", "Suresh", "Thiru", "says", "in", "an", "email", ".", "According", "to", "media", "reports", ",", "that", "personal", "information", "includes", "identity", "card", "numbers", ",", "addresses", ",", "login", "IDs", ",", "passwords", ",", "names", ",", "emails", "and", "phone", "numbers", ".", "Haveibeenpwned.com", "also", "notes", "that", "on", "JobStreet", ",", "dates", "of", "birth", ",", "genders", ",", "geographic", "locations", ",", "marital", "statuses", ",", "nationalities", "and", "usernames", "were", "also", "compromised", ".", "The", "Malaysian", "Communications", "and", "Multimedia", "Commission", "(", "MCMC", ")", "may", "have", "discovered", "the", "possible", "source", "of", "the", "data", "leaks", ",", "according", "to", "Malaysian", "Communications", "Minister", "Salleh", "Said", "Keruak", ".", "\"", "We", "have", "identified", "several", "potential", "sources", "of", "the", "leak", "and", "we", "should", "be", "able", "to", "complete", "the", "probe", "soon", ",", "\"", "he", "announced", "."], "trigger": [{"start": 16, "end": 17, "text": ["data", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 73, "end": 74, "text": ["the", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 108, "end": 109, "text": ["the", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 89, "end": 90, "text": ["The", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 176, "end": 177, "text": ["were", "stolen"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 198, "end": 200, "text": ["has", "been", "exposed"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 285, "end": 285, "text": ["compromised"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 303, "end": 305, "text": ["the", "data", "leaks"], "event": "Databreach"}], "Entities": [[{"start": 3, "end": 3, "text": ["clients"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 7, "end": 7, "text": ["they"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 22, "end": 22, "text": ["companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 20, "end": 20, "text": ["19"], "type": "Number"}, {"start": 0, "end": 0, "text": ["JobStreet"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 67, "end": 67, "text": ["3,883,455"], "type": "Number"}, {"start": 68, "end": 69, "text": ["JobStreet", "accounts"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 104, "end": 105, "text": ["Telecommunications", "providers"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 111, "end": 111, "text": ["Altel"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 134, "end": 134, "text": ["XoX"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 132, "end": 132, "text": ["Umobile"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 130, "end": 130, "text": ["Tunetalk"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 128, "end": 128, "text": ["Redtone"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 126, "end": 126, "text": ["PLDT"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 123, "end": 124, "text": ["Merchantrade", "Asia"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 121, "end": 121, "text": ["Maxis"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 119, "end": 119, "text": ["Friendi"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 117, "end": 117, "text": ["EnablingAsia"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 115, "end": 115, "text": ["DiGi"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 113, "end": 113, "text": ["Celcom"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 101, "end": 102, "text": ["telecommunications", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 95, "end": 96, "text": ["46", "million"], "type": "Number"}, {"start": 97, "end": 98, "text": ["Malaysian", "users"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 174, "end": 174, "text": ["81,000"], "type": "Number"}, {"start": 175, "end": 175, "text": ["records"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 179, "end": 180, "text": ["these", "organisations"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 188, "end": 190, "text": ["personal", "candidate", "information"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 195, "end": 197, "text": ["before", "July", "2012"], "type": "Time"}, {"start": 193, "end": 193, "text": ["accounts"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 266, "end": 266, "text": ["JobStreet"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 268, "end": 270, "text": ["dates", "of", "birth"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 272, "end": 272, "text": ["genders"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 274, "end": 275, "text": ["geographic", "locations"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 277, "end": 278, "text": ["marital", "statuses"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 280, "end": 280, "text": ["nationalities"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 282, "end": 282, "text": ["usernames"], "type": "PII"}], []], "Causal": [[], [], [], [], [], [], [], []], "Effect": [[{"start": 3, "end": 3, "text": ["clients"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 7, "end": 7, "text": ["they"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 22, "end": 22, "text": ["companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 0, "end": 0, "text": ["JobStreet"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 68, "end": 69, "text": ["JobStreet", "accounts"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 111, "end": 111, "text": ["Altel"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 134, "end": 134, "text": ["XoX"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 132, "end": 132, "text": ["Umobile"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 130, "end": 130, "text": ["Tunetalk"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 128, "end": 128, "text": ["Redtone"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 126, "end": 126, "text": ["PLDT"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 123, "end": 124, "text": ["Merchantrade", "Asia"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 121, "end": 121, "text": ["Maxis"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 119, "end": 119, "text": ["Friendi"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 117, "end": 117, "text": ["EnablingAsia"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 115, "end": 115, "text": ["DiGi"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 113, "end": 113, "text": ["Celcom"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 101, "end": 102, "text": ["telecommunications", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 97, "end": 98, "text": ["Malaysian", "users"], "type": "Person"}], [{"start": 175, "end": 175, "text": ["records"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 179, "end": 180, "text": ["these", "organisations"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 188, "end": 190, "text": ["personal", "candidate", "information"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 193, "end": 193, "text": ["accounts"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 266, "end": 266, "text": ["JobStreet"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 268, "end": 270, "text": ["dates", "of", "birth"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 272, "end": 272, "text": ["genders"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 274, "end": 275, "text": ["geographic", "locations"], "type": "Data"}, {"start": 277, "end": 278, "text": ["marital", "statuses"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 280, "end": 280, "text": ["nationalities"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 282, "end": 282, "text": ["usernames"], "type": "PII"}], []]}