{"tokens": ["TORONTO", ",", "April", "19", "(", "Reuters", ")", "-", "Global", "hotel", "chain", "InterContinental", "Hotels", "Group", "Plc", "said", "1,200", "of", "its", "franchised", "hotels", "in", "the", "United", "States", ",", "including", "Holiday", "Inn", "and", "Crowne", "Plaza", ",", "were", "victims", "of", "a", "three", "-", "month", "cyber", "attack", "that", "sought", "to", "steal", "customer", "payment", "card", "data", ".", "The", "company", "declined", "to", "say", "how", "many", "payment", "cards", "were", "stolen", "in", "the", "attack", ",", "the", "latest", "in", "a", "hacking", "spree", "on", "prominent", "hospitality", "companies", "including", "Hyatt", "Hotels", "Corp", ",", "Hilton", ",", "and", "Starwood", "Hotels", ",", "now", "owned", "by", "Marriott", "International", "Inc", ".", "The", "breach", "lasted", "from", "September", "29", "to", "December", "29", ",", "InterContinental", "spokesman", "Neil", "Hirsch", "said", "on", "Wednesday", ".", "He", "declined", "to", "say", "if", "losses", "were", "covered", "by", "insurance", "or", "what", "financial", "impact", "the", "hacking", "might", "have", "on", "the", "hotels", "that", "were", "compromised", ",", "which", "also", "included", "Hotel", "Indigo", ",", "Candlewood", "Suites", "and", "Staybridge", "Suites", "properties", ".", "The", "malware", "searched", "for", "track", "data", "stored", "on", "magnetic", "stripes", ",", "which", "includes", "name", ",", "card", "number", ",", "expiration", "date", "and", "internal", "verification", "code", ",", "the", "company", "said", ".", "Hotel", "operators", "have", "become", "popular", "targets", "because", "they", "are", "easier", "to", "breach", "than", "other", "businesses", "that", "store", "credit", "card", "numbers", "as", "they", "have", "limited", "knowledge", "in", "defending", "themselves", "against", "hackers", ",", "said", "Itay", "Glick", ",", "chief", "executive", "of", "Israeli", "cyber-security", "company", "Votiro", ".", "\"", "They", "do", "n't", "have", "massive", "data", "centers", "like", "banks", "which", "have", "very", "secure", "systems", "to", "protect", "themselves", ",", "\"", "said", "Glick", ".", "InterContinental", "declined", "to", "say", "how", "many", "franchised", "properties", "it", "has", "in", "the", "United", "States", ",", "which", "is", "part", "of", "its", "business", "unit", "in", "the", "Americas", "with", "3,633", "such", "properties", ".", "In", "February", ",", "InterContinental", "said", "it", "had", "been", "victim", "of", "a", "cyber", "attack", ",", "but", "at", "that", "time", "said", "that", "only", "12", "of", "its", "286", "managed", "properties", "in", "the", "Americas", "were", "infected", "with", "malware", "."], "trigger": [{"start": 60, "end": 61, "text": ["were", "stolen"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 69, "end": 71, "text": ["a", "hacking", "spree"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 40, "end": 41, "text": ["cyber", "attack"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 45, "end": 45, "text": ["steal"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 63, "end": 64, "text": ["the", "attack"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 94, "end": 95, "text": ["The", "breach"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 126, "end": 127, "text": ["the", "hacking"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 134, "end": 135, "text": ["were", "compromised"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 152, "end": 155, "text": ["searched", "for", "track", "data"], "event": "Databreach"}, {"start": 190, "end": 190, "text": ["breach"], "event": "Databreach"}], "Entities": [[{"start": 58, "end": 59, "text": ["payment", "cards"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 73, "end": 75, "text": ["prominent", "hospitality", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 84, "end": 85, "text": ["Starwood", "Hotels"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 90, "end": 92, "text": ["Marriott", "International", "Inc"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 81, "end": 81, "text": ["Hilton"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 77, "end": 79, "text": ["Hyatt", "Hotels", "Corp"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 16, "end": 16, "text": ["1,200"], "type": "Number"}, {"start": 18, "end": 20, "text": ["its", "franchised", "hotels"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 22, "end": 24, "text": ["the", "United", "States"], "type": "GPE"}, {"start": 30, "end": 31, "text": ["Crowne", "Plaza"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 27, "end": 28, "text": ["Holiday", "Inn"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 46, "end": 49, "text": ["customer", "payment", "card", "data"], "type": "PII"}], [], [{"start": 97, "end": 102, "text": ["from", "September", "29", "to", "December", "29"], "type": "Time"}], [{"start": 131, "end": 132, "text": ["the", "hotels"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 146, "end": 148, "text": ["Staybridge", "Suites", "properties"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 143, "end": 144, "text": ["Candlewood", "Suites"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 141, "end": 141, "text": ["Indigo"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 131, "end": 132, "text": ["the", "hotels"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 150, "end": 151, "text": ["The", "malware"], "type": "Malware"}, {"start": 158, "end": 159, "text": ["magnetic", "stripes"], "type": "Device"}, {"start": 163, "end": 163, "text": ["name"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 165, "end": 166, "text": ["card", "number"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 168, "end": 169, "text": ["expiration", "date"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 171, "end": 173, "text": ["internal", "verification", "code"], "type": "Data"}], [{"start": 179, "end": 180, "text": ["Hotel", "operators"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 186, "end": 186, "text": ["they"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 192, "end": 193, "text": ["other", "businesses"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 196, "end": 198, "text": ["credit", "card", "numbers"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 208, "end": 208, "text": ["hackers"], "type": "Person"}, {"start": 200, "end": 200, "text": ["they"], "type": "Organization"}]], "Causal": [[], [], [], [], [], [], [], [], [{"start": 150, "end": 151, "text": ["The", "malware"], "type": "Malware"}], [{"start": 208, "end": 208, "text": ["hackers"], "type": "Person"}]], "Effect": [[{"start": 58, "end": 59, "text": ["payment", "cards"], "type": "PII"}], [{"start": 73, "end": 75, "text": ["prominent", "hospitality", "companies"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 84, "end": 85, "text": ["Starwood", "Hotels"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 90, "end": 92, "text": ["Marriott", "International", "Inc"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 81, "end": 81, "text": ["Hilton"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 77, "end": 79, "text": ["Hyatt", "Hotels", "Corp"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 18, "end": 20, "text": ["its", "franchised", "hotels"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 30, "end": 31, "text": ["Crowne", "Plaza"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 27, "end": 28, "text": ["Holiday", "Inn"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 46, "end": 49, "text": ["customer", "payment", "card", "data"], "type": "PII"}], [], [], [], [{"start": 146, "end": 148, "text": ["Staybridge", "Suites", "properties"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 143, "end": 144, "text": ["Candlewood", "Suites"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 141, "end": 141, "text": ["Indigo"], "type": "Organization"}, {"start": 131, "end": 132, "text": ["the", "hotels"], "type": "Organization"}], [{"start": 158, "end": 159, "text": ["magnetic", "stripes"], "type": "Device"}, {"start": 163, "end": 163, "text": ["name"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 165, "end": 166, "text": ["card", "number"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 168, "end": 169, "text": ["expiration", "date"], "type": "PII"}, {"start": 171, "end": 173, "text": ["internal", "verification", "code"], "type": "Data"}], [{"start": 179, "end": 180, "text": ["Hotel", "operators"], "type": "Person"}]]}